Guide to the Northern Nut Growers Association records, 1892-1948
Northern Nut Growers Association records, 1892-1948
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Northern Nut Growers Association records, 1892-1948.
3426
Northern Nut Growers Association.
3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, clippings, publications, photographs, questionnaires, reports, brochures, drawings, charts, and historical sketches.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence between various members of the Northern Nut Growers Association, and between members and organizations of related scope including the California Almond Association, the Southern Nut Growers, and the United States Department of Agriculture; clippings concerning association members and activities; publications of the association and of individual members, many concerning the chestnut blight; photographs of members and of plants of interest to members; questionnaires; reports; brochures; drawings; charts; and historical sketches.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence between various members of the Northern Nut Growers Association, and between members and organizations of related scope including the California Almond Association, the Southern Nut Growers, and the United States Department of Agriculture; clippings concerning association members and activities; publications of the association and of individual members, many concerning the chestnut blight; photographs of members and of plants of interest to members; questionnaires; reports; brochures; drawings; charts; and historical sketches.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Northern Nut Growers Association.; California Almond Association.; Southern Nut Growers.; United States. Dept. of Agriculture.
Subjects:
Nuts.
Form and Genre Terms:
Charts.; Drawings.; Photoprints.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Chronological within folders.
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence from Dr. G.A. Zimmerman, 1923-1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence of Willard Bixby, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence of Willard Bixby, 1912-1916, 1927-1931, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
- Circulars, correspondence, clippings, 1909-1936 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
- Selected Nut correspondence, 1910-1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence of J.F. Jones, advertisements, 1909-1930 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence of J.G. Rush, advertisements, 1909-1917 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondence of Henry D. Spencer, 1914, 1926-1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence of James H. Bowditch, 1912-1916, 1920-1921, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, articles, presentations, ca. 1921-1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Correspondence of Willard G. Bixby, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Nut letters showing W.C. Deming's Industry, 1909-1935 (Box 1, Folder 16-19)
- Correspondence, articles, presentations, newspaper clippings, 1892-1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondence of E.A. Riehl, clippings, 1912-1931, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1911-1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, primarily with nurserymen, 1909-1915, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Correspondence of Willard G. Bixby, 1914-1917, 1931-1934 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence of Nut Growers, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1909-1922, 1929-1934 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
- Correspondence of Willard G. Bixby, articles, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Books, correspondence, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, 1899-1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence of C.A. Reed, clippings, 1926-1930, 1936-1948 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
- Correspondence of C.A. Reed, articles, 1926-1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Nut correspondence, clippings, pamphlets articles, 1908-1947 (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
- Correspondence of Robert T. Morris, clippings, 1906-1945 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
- Nut Growers Association correspondence, magazines, 1916-1946 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
- Correspondence, 1909-1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Correspondence of J. Russell Smith, clippings, advertisements, 1913-1948 (Box 2, Folder 17-19)
- Nut Growers Association correspondence, clippings, 1900-1947 (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
- Northern Nut Growers Association correspondence, clippings, 1907-1948 (Box 3, Folder 5-12)
- Nut Growing clippings, publications, 1908-1947 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Pecan promotional publications - correspondence, catalogues, pamphlets, clippings, 1909-1913 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Pomeroy English walnut - clippings, pamphlets, correspondence, 1913-1926 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Nut Growers Association correspondence, clippings, pamphlets, 1909-1941 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
- Photographs of members and plants (Box 3, Folder 19-21)